>> Thank you. Yes. So let's go to the next
question. Will the transcription work
with multiple languages? Switch within
the text.
>> Like if you want to switch like if you
want to switch while recording, you
cannot because the session has been has
to have has to be created with a
specific language. Uh so you would have
to stop the recording, start again,
record in another language. So it might
be a limitation here. However, even if
your language uh you selected another
language, but you start to speak, for
example, if you if you selected English
and you start speaking in French, for
example, the model will still pick up
what you're saying and most of the time
it will either do a proper transcription
or it will translate the transcription
in the in the language that is set up.
So, it could work.
>> We did a couple of tests also in VIP for
example whereas you have whole context
of the whole conversation at once. There
is no uh language setup. The model will
figure out the language and uh yeah
according to the tests we perform it
handles all the languages that we are
speaking in our team.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Thank you very much. So the next
question is how long will the audio
recordings be stored?
That is something also that we really
want to get your feedback on because
retention policy I know that's something
that you would like to probably uh have
options to set and we plan to just add
it in settings uh just a simple select
selector so you can um you can you can
select that time yourself
and yeah that's that's it that's
something also we need to get your
feedback on currently currently they are
stored indefinitely.
Okay. So the next question is does it
work with air?
>> Does it work with with what?
>> Does it work with air call? So I guess
it's a a very
>> I guess they are talking about one of
the providers
and
it's huh that's a nice thing about
current architecture of uh
transcriptions. It is provider agnostic.
Why? because we are not using provider
to record. We are the whole recording
happens on your site in browser.
However, that might not be long-term
solution because we would like to have
perhaps some kind of robustness. So, we
might uh switch to our own uh provider
within UDU. Uh that's uh yeah, that's
probably for the next year. At the
moment, it's agnostic provider.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So the next question is, is it
possible to remove the recordings
directly after the call
manually?
>> Uh, a little bit hackish solution, but
it exists. You can just open your
attachments because recording is just an
attachment. So you just open your
attachments and settings. I believe you